let's wait for a few people
to get in here i'm live no
no one of these days i'm going to figure
out how to use this app
but like you know it's the intro to the
stream so
my channel oh yes
the for loop challenge well it's a past
broadcast
oh yes live perfect
but like you know it's the intro let me
just uh
turn this volume down
we should have enough uh battery that
battery starts to die left to unplug the
light and then we won't have enough
light so
okay are you guys ready
for the for loop challenge
all right so the goal
of the for loop challenge because you
people always are like what's he doing
what's the goal
and we're gonna add four loops to clang
yeah yo what up what up boys
what up we're gonna add four loops to
clank
okay so let me explain so
also sws stands for smoking weed stream
so you know if you guys are taking this
as professional career advice
you're an idiot uh if you guys are
taking anything i say
professional career advice you're an
idiot
that's right okay
good evening mayfield tv um is the
smoking weed stream the weed was smoked
off stream the weed was not smoked on
stream this time
yeah that's right cringe someone sent me
an email they're like yo george you know
what would make hammer better
is if you did it as a b2b app and i'm
like you and your mba
man who cares what the business
model is
i can't even i'm too upset about it to
even talk about it
and that's why we're adding four loops
to clang okay now let me explain how for
loops work okay
so normally you have a for loop everyone
knows a four loop so i can say something
like four into i equals zero
what why is it changing my don't
change my
um
check spelling as you type no don't
check my spelling that's right
all right so let's say we have something
nice like this or i
checked my spelling as i typed oh
correct spelling automatically that's
the problem
yeah okay cool we in this we in this all
right
i don't give a about congress and
the companies dude
i don't care i don't care you know what
honestly
i even regret talking about making
hammer because you take it as a
political statement you know
it's like the masked like i don't
care man
oh yeah you should really stick it to
google i i don't care
we're making four loops alright so get
ready for what a for lupus
um sorry i wasn't streaming for the last
two days i'll show you guys what i was
doing
since it's open source i can show you i
got a contract
i got a job you know i was on some real
uh
mr peanut butter you guys know mr
peanut butter mr peanut butter is the
bojack horseman guy and he just like
shows up and he's like
is this a tv set am i in a television
show
mr peanut butter you know that guy
all right so i wrote this yeah i wrote
for for optimism the new plasma it's a
l2
uh ethereum solution um
and i wrote this so you guys can check
it out
uh three days boys three days making
money
got this apartment paid for i got my
phone bill paid
you might even to get yourself a nba
player at least to do with a car
you know all right um
bob saget what's that
what's that line oh you know you can't
say that line anymore but
funnier than you should ask bob
saget you know
never claimed that i knew how to dance i
just get drunk get hot pulled on my
pants
so five bucks just fill up my cup
don't kiss me bitch you just threw up
all right no no no no no no no we're
writing four loops all right
all right so that's a for loop so
everyone knows what this prints out
right
zero one two three four five six seven
eight
nine right okay so we're going to add a
new kind of loop
to clang it's a for loop
why'd it correct my spelling
automatically
told it not too
use the form i don't know whatever
so if you write a for loop
it's like a for loop except it does
something
a little bit different you see instead
of running this i plus plus just one
time
it runs it four times five guys burgers
and fries but it's a for loop all right
0 4 8. that's what it's going to do
right and we're going to modify clang
we're going to make a clang
that's a custom clang that's capable of
compiling
for loops you know now but real talk
whoa whoa whoa whoa don't just do i plus
equals four
you guys aren't thinking you know you
guys are thinking
we want to accomplish a goal and for
loops are the
ultimate in not accomplishing a goal and
that's what we want to do on the stream
because nobody actually
needs a for loop you know this is the
most useless thing
like if somebody proposed this in a
meeting i think even businesses that
have no taste would understand that for
loops are useless
so let's go we gotta get clang first of
all
uh let's go in chrome first we gotta
build clang
build clang let's find some instructions
um well first we can see what happens if
we try to compile
a for loop let's compile our for loop
oh we might have to add it to vim syntax
highlighting i mean i'm a little
confused you know
uh we're of course still going to need
it main none of that's going to change
yeah that looks like a nice program
right so now when i compile it we're
going to compile it with clang
oh implicit definition of function four
oh it thinks i'm making a function
i'm not making a function i'm making a
new kind of loop boys
and it's called a for loop all right so
just for reference we should have a
normal for loop
as well you know
maybe we can style this up a little bit
write a few of those and like a 4 like
that
and then a 4 like that all right now the
truth is
boys i'm not one of those cheating
streamers you know some streamers
or cheaters and they do all their
programming off stream and they're like
oh
i'm going to look really smart in front
of my audience
i'm going to actually have coded this
already off stream now honestly i
thought of this idea
my friend sent me a text message it was
like yo george
what are good books for programming and
i'm like you know what the people on the
stream ask me this all the time and the
answer is
can't learn programming from books
that's like saying that what's good
books for parkour
can learn parkour from books you know
you learn parkour by subscribing to the
parkour everyday
industry no you learn parkour by going
and smacking yourself against bars a
whole lot of times you know
and that's why i can't do parkour
because let me tell you if you could
read a book and learn parkour
man i'd be the next donna llama but
i'm not
so there's that all right
sup everybody also i'm trying to become
a twitch
partner i gotta stream six more times
over the next 20 days so i believe in us
team george hutz team tom cruise team
this twitch channel
let's go let's go all right
we're gonna have to build clang first of
all
i can download the releases from here
should we start with a release
no i think we want to start with get
yeah
that's a good choice mirror kept for
legacy
project moved it's a
mono repo
they put llvm in a mono repo
damn that's just crazy all right let's
go
this might take too long and if we get
impatient we're going to do depth one
yeah we got impatient
the next hour of the stream is compiling
clang that's true
because you know what honestly a lot of
programming is just
waiting sometimes it's thinking waiting
sometimes it's compiling waiting
sometimes it's lazy waiting sometimes
it's get checking out waiting we gotta
you know get this from the internet
do a d5 stream never subbed ever donated
many mangoes should i ban them
we'll get free entertainment around here
oh okay all right all right we go we'll
go we're good how do i build clang
configure and build llvm and clang
cd llvm project make dirt build cd build
was that the part of the stream that's
hiding
um c make dot dot slash
clang can i make clang i can't make
clang because i don't have an llvm make
lvm oh god
ziesh why do you do that for me all
right this is looking good all right
we're making progress
now of course because we're not really
lazy slackers we're going to open up vs
code vs code
is the best way if you want to read code
so we got to read the clang project you
know
this was my work on the solidities
we can just open up a
open yeah we're going to open a folder
up
not in the solidities we're in the fun
directory since this is a whole lot of
fun
we're writing for loop since the lvm
project okay cool
okay now we're going to have to figure
out where for loops or to find and clang
is probably a parser somewhere uh so the
basics of the way these things work is
you got like a parser
and then like that makes like an ast
and then after we make an ast we like
compile that and stuff
right um
c make tools would i like to configure
it no thank you
but i appreciate you asking configure
projects on opening
i don't know what configure means that
scared me you're going to like
llvm build or something all right
so somewhere there's probably
objects let me see if i can zoom in on
this for you we want everybody to be
able to see
somewhere there's probably objects
like four we gotta find wherever four is
decal c plus plus decal base wow this is
complicated as boys
i don't know how we're gonna do this did
i sign up for something that was too
hard
maybe
all right let's try searching for
four
i don't want to search files to include
clang
star
ah that's not gonna work four
oh four
oh this is gonna be harder than i
thought boys
wow look at this there's like five files
just dedicated
to to making comments
okay so well we assumed it was in the
ast let's first look at parse
parse ast oh my god this is hard
where's the grammar defined
wow this thing has more pop-ups than a
hobby king
sale
start from the front end that's a good
point i like you're thinking good man
i'm legit i'm not one of those scam
streamers who looks at it all beforehand
we are legitimately just doing this
um terribly i might add but we're doing
it
all right
well i'm in lib already
we should spend more time thinking and
less time frantically pressing
keys ast
merge
sure it's in the front end
let's take a look for things that look
like the word grammar
oh i was we're gonna we're putting music
on too this is this is a music stream
sorry for all who copyrighted
yeah i was listening to this
on the way to work but my airpods
why did this target everything
i i should have cmaked better i regret
my poor seeming
all right what are you people saying you
know what
i know what time it is really i do
something that's for the educations
uh
yeah dlvm allow projects clang yeah we
gotta do that
yeah yeah that's right yeah that's right
you know what
that's right yeah dlvm allow projects
all right that's downloading and taking
a long time
that's compiling and taking a long time
everything's taking a long time boys
who thinks my patches are good it's just
enjoyable you know like you get into
this state where you're just like
flowing through the code and you start
seeing and it's just code code code and
more
code
no it's not a for loop where i plus plus
is actually i plus equals four
because if it was i plus equals two it
would be i plus equals eight it's a
for loop where the last condition runs
four times four
does that make sense does everybody
understand
what a for loop is
all right so our goal is to add four
loops to clang
and when you ask why you're asking a
stupid question
and like like you know what sometimes
sometimes
things get a little bit close to being
useful and when things are a little bit
close to being useful you guys think oh
why oh would this be good should we sell
this as a b2c product or a b2b
product i don't know man maybe
businesses could use
for loops that could help them get 20
more tps reports on their leveraged
printer buyouts
that's right you want an example of a
for loop right there
now unfortunately no language supports
the great for-loop holy i am terry
davis
no language supports the great for-loop
construct
and that's why we're adding it in
there's many stupid questions check my
bio i even
reference stupid questions
anyone who told you there were no stupid
questions probably also taught you to
read
by just looking at the words instead of
being able to recognize them you know
okay we have llvm now now hopefully we
can just do make on clang and it's gonna
work
this isn't gonna that's useless this is
a second
oh sure i want to delete all two files
cmake dot slash clang
dlvm enable projects equals clang
maybe this will work fingers crossed
no llvm config llc
wait oh compilers
you find you may need to set those
things does that fix it
oh my god fine
is that 88 already yeah build all of
llvm
go do that then we're still going to
have to build clang add installation
prefix of lvm to cmic prefix what
do i have any lvm config.cmake
oh yes here we go
welcome to attitude
cmig prefix path hey
now we're talking boys now we're talking
i don't know what we're testing here but
it's got to be important
let me copy and paste no don't run away
yeah good
what just happened
like that i don't like any of it
hmm it didn't work
unknown c make command is this because i
need a newer cmake
well that's going to upset me
or is that because i need a newer llvm
so
do plugins let's try
plugins
no
oh
this is a tragedy
it didn't work they have to like make
the versions match or something
it knows i care too much yeah i know so
sat with me
all right we're building llvm
that was a waste of time let's just be
patient you know sometimes you just need
patience
now i still don't know you guys saw me
modify the par sir
i modified the ast thingy we now have
this statement here
um
but i think that would i like to use a
compile commands json to auto configure
and tell us
this thing really has so many pop-ups
this we're going to have to make a full
discarded ah
you know what how do the parts get
stitched together
wow act on for statement
clang is mad complex boys
oh my god yeah of course i need a cogen
for the amd
gpu yes that's very important i'm so
glad you built that
i can figure out what version of lvm we
have and then rebase my thingies on top
of it
all i really wanted was clang you know
which version of lem do i have
lvm version 10.0 a
lvm 10.0 download the playing source
what am i doing chat read the what am i
doing
or what am i doing
if you don't no goal
alright we know about that error but we
got that error
fixed with that
fingers crossed boys is it going to
build oh this finished anyway
i don't know i don't trust it i trust
this one
oh never mind
what can this version of lvm not build
this version of lvm
no that's too much man i don't know what
we're gonna do if that's true
all right let's go in here let's go to
build
two and then we'll go to build two and
then we'll type cma dot dot slash clang
wait what how did that work that wasn't
supposed to work
yeah that's what i was supposed to get
now we can just add
llvmdir
oh bills
there we go
what
this because i broke it
unexpected input at top level i think i
might have broken that
so
okay
mini raid what up why does this work
could not find
include llvm option opt
parser
where is that thing
it's in llvm include opt parser
why is files not found oh
maybe
how do i build clang
do i have to build it in the same thing
there's no point here i don't know what
if i just uh for this i did cmake.slash
llvm
and then maybe i need to enable clang
but this is gonna bitch and be like oh
you already did a c make here oh no
playing project is enabled okay cool wow
it's targeting everything i don't need
all those targets there's too many
targets
okay i don't know what it's doing now
wow look at all that stuff that it's not
building oh good i think this is clang
obviously take forever to rebuild them
okay it's building clang now we're
making good progress
it took a long time should we the only
question
is are we going to submit a pull request
at the end of this
ops trying to upstream the for statement
uh no i don't watch i don't care what
basil
zuckerberg have to say look it's like
who cares what are they gonna do
you know
whenever i hear the phrase you're with
us or you're against us
i usually hate both those things i'm
usually both against them
and against the people who say those
things you know
ah
bro if you care too much you lose i mean
that was like relationship theory 101.
oh too few arguments to function call
now we're talking all right now we got a
real bug
all right real bug let's go fix it par
statement
because we have multiple calls to parse
for statement
um we should really add to parser.h
the fact that everybody knows for
statements are always
true uh no i'm i'm not enlightened
centrist me
i'm um
i'm detached that's the word detachment
i'm a detachment man you know if the
commies want to come and
take over i'll put my hammer and sickle
flag up if the nazis want to take over
i'll hang my swastika dutifully
that's right
as long as they you know leave me alone
and that's all that matters man you know
that's
all that matters just take who's ever in
power
and you know accept it because that's
the truth about it you know you can try
to like fight it
but then you're just the guy in the
billy joel song man
[Music]
all right i think can we build now did i
fix the bug
now it's going to have to build a lot of
things because i changed a dot h file
maybe not let's go
all right the dream is when we'll be
able to do dots let oh
where do my bins go
my bins are gone
does it rebuild all the bins every time
no it can't do that there's too many
bins for that
wow this takes a long time to build
oh that's because we're in clang source
that was a failed experiment
we gotta go in here to build ben oh
they're all my bins take a look
that's so many bins
build bin clang test.c
oh that's going to be a great day when
that works and that day is going to be
soon
you defaulted 4 to true that's a great
choice that's a great catch
we got to make it false because if it's
true
all my statements will be four
statements and then four statements just
won't be special and how will we have
our
competitive edge business thing
493 viewers hello
should we uh should we let everybody
talk again
am i allowed to show my money on twitch
did we figure that out or not
what's this person saying yo can you
unban me no
all right no the answer is no well i
don't make that much money on twitch
but i do want to be a twitch partner
because think about it you know what i
mean
there's got to be people out there who
work hard to climb that ladder their
whole life they're like
i just want to be a twitch partner i saw
a guy at twitchcon
and he was so excited when he got twitch
partner and it's just like something i'd
like to casually do
you know because to win
is not to care because if you care you
lose
some guy in the comments said that
wow this takes a long time to build
i do like check marks you know i
the primogen is the top coding streamer
redefinition of default argument oh you
can't do that i see
i already made it false over here
we're gonna make a false over there
do we have a clang yet no fine yet
we are very nlvm though that's pretty
cool we made this lvm from scratch
wow version 12.
yo that's a crazy version
twitch partner comes with an exclusive
clause no they couldn't actually do that
no way you guys are joking man
let's google that
it was too easy to apply for for them
just uh
the twitch part partners
the twitch partnership program for those
who are committed to streaming
this twitch partner you'll have access
to the following benefits
no it doesn't say anything about being
exclusive to twitch
you guys make a lot of dumb up man
i'm not trying to you know
disrespect anybody here like that you
know like
like sign that kind of disrespect but
i am saying that i don't think that's
true uh oh
i'll have to act as a role model to the
community though
i don't currently meet the weight no
hang on i don't know what that means
that's a vague term vague term
streamers who complete the path to
partner achievement in your achievements
dashboard will unlock a button i have
that button
but i haven't streamed
12 times in the last 30 days
the minimum criteria we look for in
potential partners
and completing them doesn't guarantee
partnership
uh all right so someone was saying there
was some
there was some youtube comment where
some guy said he was going to challenge
me to some
coding game what was it called
twitch affiliate program yeah i don't
know about i'm not part of the affiliate
program
just stop and restart the stream no i
think it's days
code clash i think that's it all right
let's go
we gotta i mean we gotta wait for it to
compile anyway what else are we doing
all right
join a clash oh already i gotta sign up
i'm upset
oh let's go how do i play
well i better figure it out i got 90
seconds okay let's go
i've never played this game before so i
don't know what to do
all right you have to pass the number
maximum number test with the lowest code
size
okay you must output the end first two
elements
n1 and n2 were given the element with
n index n is the sum of the previous two
elements
what
oh i see
uh okay so it's a fibonacci crap thingy
um we have uh
we need a we need a ring buffer thingy
oh you know what does it even matter it
might not even matter um
for all right we'll just say n a
equals that or i
in range n or while length of n a is
less than
n
print n a sub n minus one
or an a sub minus one n a dot append
and then all right
oh it didn't work first number given
what
i'll put the third element oh
so this should be yeah n a n minus one
yeah no
oh my god i'm not i'm losing this game
aren't i
yeah all right go
what do they mean by shortest
i don't even know
yeah i'm winning
oh i think i should have oh i had to
write it really short
oh i say leased bites
oh my clang's built
yeah i won that's right number one
number one i'm number one that's right
that's right
okay do we have a clang
oh we have a clang now back to our
regularly scheduled program
fatal error standard io's not found
well no one really needed standardio
anyway did they
oh it built okay all right that was good
progress
if you'll notice despite don't worry
about standard io that wasn't that
important
but if you notice it's almost correct
except for the fact that
the for loop is of course behaving
identically
to the for loop that's four with four
letters
is behaving identically to the four with
not four letters loop so we need
to fix that bug of course now
i'm not sure really how to do it this is
the hardest part
we have an extra results
we have a bunch of options for where we
can like add things and i don't know if
these things add but
make full value make full discarded
value expression
this is a full expression arc
act on finish full expression discarded
value
true
we might actually have to pass it in to
act on four statements
we can pass in whether what kind of for
loop it is if it's a four with
how many letters and then
we want to look at full x for r third
check break continue binding check for
redundant iteration
x per third well let me just try a
little something first and see if it
works
um i mean this isn't this would work in
c as well
so am i allowed to put like multiple
things here
not like that but what if i put them in
these things
it's not allowed i feel like there's a
way to do two things there though
man did i pick something unadmittedly
really hard
return new context for statements
sub experts inc
hmm
four state statement for statement class
let's see the for statement class
so where's the thingy that actually
makes it a for statement
check break continue binding third dot
get
expert third third blah blah blah
for statement okay
so we set all these sub-experts we have
to use
ink somewhere else
like where do we maybe we have to find a
code gen for this
oh
set inc
wow
i really keep this like
here we go codegen
increment is essentially part of the
body but it needs to include
all right let's just try this see if it
works
and then we'll have to figure out how to
pass it all the way through to there
you'll have to modify the for statement
to see if it's actually a four statement
i shouldn't name them something else so
when i say it it doesn't say the same
word over and over again
but this is what we're doing in case you
guys like goal
hmm
i think it worked
i know that meg didn't finish yet
to be fair i don't really know what uh
cogen pgo what's a pgo
pgo implementation i don't know about
that
statement printer ast reader
that looks nice
mark
walk ast check security syntax
sema statement
i don't know what sema is either
well let's look in code gen and see what
we can find
sin includes
lib cogen cg expert
four
and we'll look at includes
hmm cg
function as well
code gen function
okay so somewhere we're creating this
thing
called a for statement and if i wanted i
could pass all the stuff down
um
oh well this actually breaks it if it's
a four statement so we don't do that
how did that work at all with that
broken
okay um
let's try a quick test
that should throw the assert
okay yeah
not a for statement okay cool
that's why we have that there
make full discarded value expression
it's an expression like i don't really
want an expression
let's just treat it like for some reason
this doesn't work
and we're gonna have to create and act
on forced i mean i might be able to hack
it there
but then do we really learn and what is
this about but learning okay
so we made a for statement in the ast
context so we have this thing called for
statements
um
what's a friend class
all right public statement blah blah
blah
get inc get body reinterpret cast
to expression i don't really see a way
to do it there either
there has to be something that's doing
matching on this
which is uh outputting stuff
transforms ast importer here's statement
printer
little code gen function
that doesn't look useful cogent pgo
looked the most useful
with this visit four statement thing
what is code gen profile guided
optimization well it can't be that
in coverage mapping gen rewrite
objective c
par statements
oh
cg statement open m oh here we go what's
this a mid
for statement oh now we're talking oh
yeah boys
yeah i think we're looking somewhere all
right perfect
if there's an increment emitted next
okay
if it's a for statement we omit it four
times
okay this is it cg statement i think we
found it
and then we're just gonna have to wire
it up so we pass that through
and then we've made the best clang in
the world with the addition of the for
statement
and then we'll fork it we'll submit a
pull request and we'll see if they
accept it
oh yeah oh yeah zero
four eight if you guys would notice in
the
what i'm doing that was the expected
behavior boys
so now we just got to pass it through
all right
so we have a const for statement
so let's just add a if
s dot is for statements
um where is this thing defined
always be building abb
um par
statement okay actions act on for
statement
we're going to want to add his for
statement here
here at the four statement
is for statements
when we create a for statement we'll
just go here like
that now we need to fix
this uh wow those are source locations
yeah
and now let's go find this actual
constructor
like statement.c or something
yeah let me just say
for statement
equals is for statement
boom c plus plot oh no
why is it building so much stuff
no
okay so we added this for statement and
now we probably have to add it in
okay i added it in there where did we
not add it in the action
thing so wherever acton4 statement is
declared i think we have to
here
it's in semi
i hope it's still built
taking forever to build again
you want to just do another for loop
inside
um
all right you guys you know what
you all get you'll get
yeah you could use commas that's a good
point
but you're right it was thomas
you almost got a pass for all the
non-subscribers but you didn't
all right so i think we just got to be
patient again let's play clash of code
let's go
i didn't win
i have five minutes to write tiny ass
code all right
all right let's go
why did i have to rebuild the whole
thing
you get it right now let's play collage
of code
no it failed
this argument to member is for statement
no what did that say oh my clash of code
is coming in
over this function is not marked const
oh i see
oh what is this reverse mode
oh it's just power i think is it power
it's not power
2 4 is 16.
but 7 to the 11 is not that
it's almost power
i would think it's a different base
wow that's pretty brutal
okay
well
539 over 7 is 77.
oh so is it just 2 times 2 times 4 and
like 7 times 7 times 11
and 456 times 456 times 54.
yeah okay now do we gotta make it tiny
again
or does it not matter it's just m times
m times n i think
i'll make it tiny just because we can
do you got to go tinier like it's a
little unfair what if like my
boilerplate to parse it isn't as tiny
actually it's python three do i really
need oh if i change it to python two
well i can't have python two never mind
this is why i can't have nice things
got so many bites it's a little shorter
i guess
wait it was just time yo that's
i wasted time
no i'm not interested don't try to sell
me on your
it's not constant it's got to be
constant
constable is for state
is that better
i don't understand why it's got to
rebuild everything now
warning const type qualifier on return
type has no effect
oh i have to like put it here don't i
oh god i don't know any c plus
and if you edit this thing it seems like
everything has to rebuild it's a
nightmare
okay more clash of code
yeah let's go let's go no stop trying to
sell me a job
go go go go
okay reverse mode again
um some of them have an
x next to them and some of them don't i
think just the odd numbers do and the
even numbers don't yeah that seems
pretty easy okay
uh 4i in
oh n equals input sub i
if n mod 2 equals 1
print
else
that i know this one's just a race
i'll test cases boom
what i lost
all right let's go let's go let's go
come on
[Music]
for each integer i'll put the number of
ones in its binary representation okay
let's go let's go let's go um
bin x uh filter
lambda x x equals equals one
uh comma bin x
uh list spin x uh
length list filter uh
rat equals print rat all right let's go
little test cases sometimes you just got
to be ballsy and oh no it's shortest
coat again no
oh my god i could have wrote much
smaller
ah does my clang take forever to build
how do i know if it's short okay i guess
the ones where it's reverse it's
quickest
and then the ones where it's the other
one it's
uh
let's go let's go let's go
come on reverse come on i can beat you
at speeds boys
shortest mode okay pass the most test
with the shortest code side fine that
means we can take more time
i have 15 minutes what is this a chess
game
one line containing
and the number of elements one line
containing
n numbers the sequence after being
shifted
right so first we'll read any of this
and we can just say
input there to consume that
what do you mean by shifted oh a left
shift
okay um
what
can only concatenate list not string to
less
and see the error
all right can we write it shorter
i feel like it's just unfair because
you know i bet you there's some language
where it's like in instead of input
that's cheap
oh some people are using c plus plus i
pity them
too few arguments being sent to yeah
okay we gotta fix this bug
all right let's go that's pretty short
i'm pretty happy with that
55 characters that's gonna lose i can
tell already
true few arguments to function calling
tree transform
uh well you know what we should really
make the function call have a default
[Applause]
let's make it work okay and then where's
that action one as well
that should work maybe
no euler she
jolly
all right let's get a fastest one so i
can just win
i don't like this shortest code game
oh reverse mode yes okay
um
it's like 64 times 63
yeah that's right okay good so it's just
um
a times a times
a minus one little test cases
let's go yes sucka dick dumb shits
yeah this one was fun that's right
winning
um this game is stupid and it's just a
way to try to sell your job
it takes forever to build oh my god like
who built this
how does anybody work on this code
if i didn't set my like equals false
right yeah that's probably why you're
not supposed to put those things in
headers
i don't know does anybody work on this
code
i think my for loop is pretty done who
thinks it works
did i make it work
three to death
okay we add it there pool is four
statement cons
for a statement there
parse it if it's called normally it just
returns zero
here that will inherit the
the false which is set there if it's a
for statement do that
parse it we know that's correct i don't
know why i deleted the fix me i guess it
was a stupid fix me
what's the for loop challenge well you
know about four loops but what about for
loops
right you've got to add four loops to
clamp so we're going to compile this
beautiful code here
and right now both four and four loops
are acting like for loops but
look zero four eight you see we just
want a for loop to be zero for it
because in a for loop
it runs this statement four times
so this is equivalent to this
but with lower case eyes yeah
oh let's go let's go let's go
that's right
it's taking too long
you shall have fun everyone's a winner
even if zero percent
of the
i'll discover coding game for tech
hiring oh i knew it was just a hiring
funnel
never mind oh there we go
oh i can launch it
no it's not i equals four we're gonna
once my for loops work i'll demo them
for you or the clash has already started
let's go fastest number tests and the
best possible all right cool
um the hexadecimal
hexadecimal triplet okay cool so we want
to say color 1
3 we want to say hex 0
plus color 1 3 r equals that
g b this can be 3
5 3 4 5 7
print r print g print b
right play all test cases it didn't work
um stir object cannot be interpreted as
integer uh who was trying to interpret
anything as an
integer oh no that's hex that's not what
we want we want to say
int comma 16 god i lost this
play all test cases yeah let's go
oh
you don't run the loop four times guys
none of you all
understand the syntax of the for loop
and we're gonna have a lesson and we're
gonna teach you all how to use for loops
after my new improved clang finishes
building with support for for loops
wow i really i really shout all over
this code you know
they'll never upstream this into clang
oh my god it's building llvm again
wow it's really this was not next time
we do a challenge like this maybe we'll
do a challenge like this tomorrow so we
do another challenge tomorrow
we're still working on busy beaver but
those are the long serious streams those
aren't smoking weed streams
smoking weed streams we just do dumb
maybe tomorrow
we'll like i don't know
oh i know what we're gonna do tomorrow
got four loops for gcc yeah that one's
even more of a nightmare
i don't know this clang takes forever to
build though i guess it's all written in
c
plus and klang's really slow bass clang
oh should we play more this game is kind
of boring
oh why didn't i call it four because i
don't know it's a for loop
should i do a live lead code contest
did that i think did i do lead code on a
stream oh my god it really wow
this this is just it's hard to look at
like this is just oh my god stop putting
in your funnels people you know
i don't like funnels i'm claustrophobic
you know what i wish
i wish like when i read a website like
this
like like just anybody are there people
in the world
who look at that website and like are
like
wow google was founded on the belief
that everything we do
should always respect the user if i ever
make a website that looks like that
somebody needs to slap me man
you know hack the planet does anybody oh
wow look at this oh it's three women
looking at a google pixel phone
oh that makes take that makes me feel
good about google
you know
oh oh my clang is done oh that's more
exciting than this but let's go let's go
let's go
fast fast fast okay uh the length of one
number of regular one unit what
one will be split into six triangles two
will be split into 24
triangles
probably scales with some kind of square
thing
i don't know is it just n squared times
uh six
yeah victory no one's beaten that time
come on come on oh
yeah and the for loops work oh who loves
my for loops
you see when you run a for loop it only
runs the incrementer once but when you
run a for loop
it runs the incrementer so people are
like oh well it's the same as i plus
four right so let me change it to i plus
four you think these two things are
going to behave identically
well that actually that's probably not a
good test you know you probably want
that and yeah that is going to behave
identically but what if you do
i plus equals two here
it's not i plus equals four it's
actually i plus equals eight
oh okay stop complaining to me how many
of these did i win
four out of seven what
i don't know man all right but we made
four loops work
now what should we use our newfound for
loop for it's kind of a useless loop
but like i think if we call a function
in here
can we like do printies
it's gonna run that oh wow runs out a
lot of times
oh especially if we don't increment i
yeah you see you see how it printed
print
four times for each um
for each iteration through the for loop
we're gonna call this one super four
oh yeah so does everybody understand the
syntax
it runs this four times if you have a
for loop
we did it stop the clock lots of
printies
if you guys want you can manually type
out this diff that's about to scroll
across your screen
stop beeping at me you can manually type
out this diff and you too
can have four statements in your clan
um let's get diff
into temp claw
how do i copy it to the clipboard
mac copy file to clipboard
pb copy oh
i will call it clang for
dot diff add
support for four loops
to claim
all right enjoy my beautiful gist
ah
um we can feel forever ashamed about
removing this fix me
it was a stupid fix me anyway but there
you go boys
there you go i hope you enjoyed no q a
tonight
uh i'm done with q a because you guys
ask stupid questions
all right good night everybody i'll see
you all tomorrow bye bye streams
bye bye bye